[Music]
béarnaise sauce if you is really not
good to build the house of the Lord
where you say that is also Pecola house
of prayer house of worship and that is
what we come to do today not latekka to
kusuda away marijuana
Yelena mo mo mo mo mo mo many faux-tina
new Maserati Allah Athena Buddha compass
Aoife mana is pikake honest I look up
okay Asifa
[Music]
see MA
[Applause]
[Music]
ha ha
[Applause]
[Music]
to see me
the Moscow fool vanadium Gaza
let's go from cool and I just a fool
[Music]
your excellency the president deputy
president our presiding bishop guest
speaker presiding bishop elect our
entire members of parliament who are
with us distinguished guests and all the
congregation's wanna see fewer who who
who is sue I want to welcome you to
African lunch at Mill Imani for today's
historic occasion
today our presiding bishop elect the
Reverend Habra mullah and his deputy the
Reverend Paul Crewe he will be installed
to check on the leadership of the church
we want to congratulate both of you as I
similar money and wish you God's
blessings we want to thank God for the
presiding bishop
Silas Yeager for his leadership and
giving the church a smooth transition I
simile money has been your church as the
presiding bishop and we want to wish you
God's blessings as you transition to
serve Him in other capacities to all our
guests who have come feeling the
presence of our Most High God let us
celebrate his goodness as we worship Him
together
you
Akua Barras aku Lakhan is Allah for
Allah Church Kenya la cucina Seco de
Mitrano Tirico minute on Oh Wesley hue
January Makkah while she really McCoy
villainous irony no liquor on tawa
Keisha conchagua cassis Abraham Allah
who as kofuku Mahalo per sec Reverend
dr. Silas Diego now hi-yah - wa kafa Tia
Sharia naturally booze ot zilla's oh
well qua Sasha to the final ba de ya
come waka waka Huia Oscar from ku nanny
named Carrie bishop as go from Cornell
staff who Reverend dr. Silas a go along
goes a bada the quake wakfu Akira Nkosi
see massimo Gizella as kofuku AIC
tanzania pimalia nasco from comb staff
ooh Daniel in iguana early from work a
wakfu Oscar from Cumbre Moroni
[Music]
vasee CC moscow few qualms a penci among
go
Katka who do my iguana es su Cristo
whoa-hoa opera Saku la Africa inland
charge Kenya no integrity no aluminum
water Mulyani Cahaba sakuya Elio Pomona
byung-ho see why schmira a Miami gucchy
le to abou top emerges alam Samui TG
salami on go
Santana Sasha
Natasha mama and eco man decoy
animatronic at Isaiah Co now Israel MO
tommy chong go yo Kapo nelly a couch
aqua Musa Ibrahim Oh Rafi Kiang go way
way
Nelly ago chica toga misha dunya naka
quita token Pemba zakir naik Wamba wave
a home to Michigan go
Demi Gooch aqua voila sicko kotoba you
co copy wanna me many Pomona now a Yusuf
Atta a gay vemana me Managua Co
netiquette Thien Kofu Nami net ACOs idea
nam metal ashika qualms Okinawa
kumahachi
yang go Tennessee Allen or among cat
acacho hana come anata no non hola mundo
la CIMA say glisteny
nino la Moo goo goo toga NGO hanim
Tecate fo
cinema Leone aqua Mimi valet me Minelli
Oh a Jaguar Nene nominee koa welcome
when mocha say matanda na ma tuned ano
hepatica car I am BA voila lot
mumble Oh Papa question Arango a penny -
amber
mangu - ilium Tecate foo Mungo Mlle
Julia toka nakute Akasha quad amo Yamaha
Gwenda Gwen Ben WA Yesu Cristo - nakusha
carrucha wing you are Emma Navarre
Akasaka Neffe piety beauty will leave
you to carry me sass otaku see a banner
from Omaha Maria - yucky Rojo nakushita
Ksenia sorrow say - lily - choo hemipene
ciacco - Kiko to makea quaff raha Ali
- kiichi Vega tre waka to accrue
taquamenaw pendra category stay ESO
Guanajuato a Scavo avraham eluamous mama
Bella Jimenez Mungo nom bellyache Aneesa
le wacko wacko
well DOMA Yas kofuku lockni le way
pamoja La si si - potato Tov Akari
you Tecate few am we tofu to sukira oh
no Janine hola mundo de Matteo Kwanzaa
in a common energy vaca cumin heceta you
see eye to eye - Mia Kurama
Leo Leo Madonna Yakko julio para wanna
pee knock waka waka ama Kanoa now say we
artifact re hiya
okay Atika hiya eloquent Alessa qua kho
qua Tahiry guava - what a insane of
sayako naka fondest Mukunda choco Domo
Attica Mambo hiya
Monica Kohana he vo Utah choco enough
ciacco Nawal a wok Ezekiel do co-op
rahamallah
who made it - Ana mangu
which acqua Liana Buraku Africa inland
ChaCha's koku J Hunico Valley
Kashyyyk owatta beikoku
were up Africa inland church Kenya do
knocking Bali shangilia am
[Applause]
[Music]
Oscar formula jae-hoon occupy Lake
Wanaka see Namaskar foo and Ino an
African inland church Kenya eloquent
Alessa my Oh baby
yeah walk off ooh one more course way to
you so crystal comma me - hi to mama
Joaquin de la mangu do Valley
[Music]
do go as control a Nakula Zambelli among
go Nam bellyache Aneesa una Copa like
watchin Adamu Baba one on aramta cattivo
kupaka
uh tamiya yeah Oscar from ku naquan
galley aqua auto mahi in a tune son
catechol a jumbo ilmu a to good sway
noir to while away do knock on valley
henderson
yo como la voix Coppola goes mama de
maua Nino Tecate fue la Mungo Nakula
soma Colosseo nakusha Nana na Kela
fundació Lonardo pataka ohanga Leah
McKinney Yakko a crystal so albury way
sahaba kwaka Fatih nanana Mungo Naruto
Mitaka TiVo Satan's a comma
yay Olivia quad is I do know Polly
yo como la una Kobayashi nyesha alien
phenomena
yeah my Makua Kayla mucho do knock on
Valley
Sansa naga chicken Kanako manga casa da
musica ha t he c neuron Tecate Phu
Hanukkah can see na ho Toma Naha now a
qua can see na who Toma yahwah's ko
katakana zalimoon una yo Capitao
assassin Quaqua KO a Meccano yet
question among go papa mana neuro- ooh
[Music]
now on borrow this way a violation
Yakutia two more bear
[Music]
thank you Thank You number s : at ASCO
full GUI GUI hapa 2-1 be asked of way to
good
now ELISA wakil away two years ago Tom
Anunnaki Abu Dhabi Waikele okay
with presiding bishop it's a Hornet to
invite you to me me ask of you Abraham
agua de chapala wanna Chama Cha
brassicas kofuku Africa in LAN charge
Kaena Kaena careful my own mango no
cojes oh no bongos ooh aramta catchy few
among go now come Bali kopaka knock you
take Lisa or Duma lamaa Giacomo no ambit
Anna Navarro was asked of mucho Nayak
Wamba Anita Phoenicia Kozma Mia na
Pacheco amania bono a tree so Cristo
mrs. Inga Tia modely nama Rudy Carmen
Olivia can you Nina destory the Africa
in lands charge Kenna now come below
Fung WA naka teba Nash area a canoe nazo
teza Barossa KU
Africa in land charge Kenna was I
younggu the metrically he Appa AIC will
man later a share in the sea Thomas was
January
Kartika Marco a burn away 2 years of
crystal while L familiy nation
[Music]
Bishop moolah is now officially
installed as a presiding bishop of a
African in line charge Kenya
[Applause]
[Music]
- amber Parker OH - Mungo
paavo Arahama when yes a I append oh you
see unaccompanied croco tuba
Minako eso Cristo amo così WeDo
imbibe a taco token boa quoc oofah naka
muka crois que na kappa too big Unni
acababa de boa vehice kusuda a Jenga
Kanazawa que algo ito ang Maremma to me
no engine a quaver Angeles no engine
equable mo tuna go see hey monk way to
kuala moto Mitsuko oz kahlúa an abacus
aza Kwas kofuku Rojo a competitive na o
Malaysia time appear in July
Amani company my a galatin saucony
Sulaco casue t a super muy valley a
chenge hacia arriba valley high body
ohms ideally Asiago to me a dramedy
Anunnaki poly Adam Osama Naga topic re
na na na KO Wamba knocks Ollie
wanna knock upon Dejah um Satya gotta go
to couvreux oddity boo katha kaadu
samavaya avocados anniversary casue t a
eunuch on a quantum issue akan when you
pendo xie na na ha Achille moi mean if
katha kaadu to Morocco nayaki ing Attica
for i am le Quoc rooster a soup wanna
wait oh I she normally keep emotion away
wrong talkative Oh mangu Moira me Layla
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
so Anita bombers in Moscow Kotoko when
the moon imagine metabiotic Waka's
indeed
[Music]
Sasha nua Katia
Cooper on Imam lock Mamluk ayah Kwanzaa
he'll miss Elia Africa in lunch at now
Cooper a way
we're longoza Kanazawa Africa inland
charge nanana na Mugu
[Music]
Putin goes a Kanazawa Africa England
charge- Ayaka second is a la Africa
inland China by law sake
[Music]
naca takashi-kun ammonia once you are
duly registered as the presiding bishop
of a IC certificate Yaga ego haba we are
tax compliant
your excellency nasa-tv kaitiaki ego
haba haba Cunha pin number
Jurgen insula Africa inland charge Villa
villa Appa Cunha registration yellow
Viet Louviere to Amber Monona Gattaca
para para mi querida stat Negev men of
Kenya
so I'm handing over these documents to
you now a certificate say Garza
certificate Lacroix a little query just
at 1952 so so those few remarks my
brother and my friend you are now the
presiding bishop
[Applause]
[Music]
last now Alissa waging a war to Africa
England charge was her mommy watching
light you water miss mommy
once a mushy anjali iguana
[Music]
now Alissa watch unity wat away I see
now John Huizenga no animate a hero's
engine a JIT goes mama new Maya's cough
when Abraham Ulloa nakum's idea catechol
a jumbo attend acasi a lyokha pto
assassin c'mon he vo Nia insane men do
Magua to satya a man wash ricotta to
smoke imagine imagine guys voic-- Ricky
walk on Islay I see no I see Ricky vato
a crystal soon as kofuku Abraham agua a
magical iguaçu young Jose Kanazawa
Africa inland Tatiana heavy OS Iroquois
designation analamanga Lana vo same
achoo yahushua vato mahi yes you a
Lovato monofin sawaki cuando bill nano
lamu Alice a Mojave our a sickness a
Nene and a single is a Mimi
nyaaaah cattle Nene Anika Tommy me nyan
cat I'm a homo kata yay Ali Natoma
why she wrote a kamikaze ibotta him
alone yeah a Wacka Wacka foo a scoffer
mama
Jos Cherokee Muta Cherokee onon a moat
ammonia common evo new hi bunny do Moo
goo Otto's idea
wanna Alberici wanna our Lindy wanna our
own go see Amina Cathy teeny Yamato
Barraza qu una multa de caminha turn on
whether a January Morocco l villainous
greenie Killam chikuwa cassis appalled
crew quan ibis kofuku Mohali Bacchus is
a brahmana now Coco up Sharia certain a
charitable daughters delivered to our
new okati salsa welcome welcome back fo
na na mo kharabeesh Athena ASCO from ku
Reverend dr. Silas llegó hace para wakfu
a key one score food yo forget your mask
off from come staff Oh Daniel noon wanna
wear a CT le wake a wakfu neighbors go
from ku until a cuz his hip or carry I a
caribou
[Music]
good Sanderson thank you very much yeah
chaotic when engi the Messiah DC what is
a few to obey - moon to pavilion go see
Madonna Allatoona kyung-ho see amber
magically waa-waa-waa scoff - nakuru
amaze mama bellyache oh you choke wanna
naughty react hombre que todo para que
sort a query so Chris Tavano ed Dukas
Koval grew a homer to Ana Mungo Nava
calcula wanna Chama Cha para Saku Koivu
as kofuku while africa inland charged
jae-hoon ago ballet Ishita what fun when
a EBU s kofuku were Africa inland church
Kenya beyond chang li na
ask of GUI jae-hoon occupy like afonya
kasi Pomona's kofuku eloquent less Amuro
BD Yaakov nana city symphonic a/c NASSCO
from Italy most Spanish I see yellow
birria walk off one more causeway to you
so crystal come mom which engage him
Emma alia eat one among go beyond Mina
now listen I appear would you have a
coupla Pellicer consequent of Alicia an
alloy which a coruña me me yeah ganna go
go
[Music]
okay a malama kuriboh
Malika Bishop our rainfall crew Amy as
Kofu only a jackal WA one i bo kho kho
kho qua Africa Elan charge Kenya oh yeah
keV oh boy on a mango cual es oh no
Volvo see quorum Tecate faux pas mundo
la Cubana kopaka na cuticle laser mod
mod a macho como yo te na batana na diva
when I do ask Ivanko Namba Rita's ideas
kofuku Oh Africa a language Kenya Oh
Felicia Noguchi Kimani iguana when Tia
so christo.pas funda show general among
go , Livio kanuni nada story Africa in
language Kenya lock you believe agua na
kotoba Syrian economy so a Sbarro's aku
Africa in Lanka Kenya wasa he angle
matura collie Yabba a simile money
Liotta Regina citizen worry
katika marker wanna wear two years of
crystal were McCullough album Bellini
[Applause]
[Music]
Reverend Paul QE now officially
installed in wenatchee Mongolia to
Pagani sauna byeongguk a tunic Wambach
wanna knock a few Auto miyamoto Mexico
as kofuku II am biomimetic opt aqua ven
go sue Akane Sulaco naive Oh Vasco from
coup Walken is a lie I see Jessie Anangu
vozack yo ho Chi Minh Abu Saleh o ADC my
ahkahuna kana Enomoto moon as idea Kyung
go see and buy a maraca Kilowog Katya on
Akane retiree comes idea to Nam America
a wok full cat occasional among go Baba
one and room tacit evil amen
wanna
acabar EK phnom kulen day wonna Wonga
0rk narco Fedele wanna aquino Leo so VAR
k now Cooper Imani kwan-jin hola mundo
Baba namana neurone talkative
[Applause]
[Music]
- Shankly our banner -
we are going to have a parade from all
the bishops presencia who jaboticaba
negated imagina calm MP MP oh we want
our visitas to know who you are
caribou knee bishop soy el camera quad
McAfee Bishop cotton West Oh God
Bishop on th South Nyanza Bishop
Maharaja Bay Bishop Joaquin Winkie
mischievous engine Anthony Wayne Bishop
go corner Oh pshaw moutoku John Darwin
fish table Matata Marsabit vision window
chewy fish Moo goo yo Machado's
missionary taxi bishop yogamaya Eldoret
assistant bishop Westmacott
tankobon kenya piece of jewelry central
mission womb' McWeeny fish semester
olive oil fish oil omega g Otto
Bishop John Bannon D Bishop Tadros
a kettle Malvina toga miss over Manitoba
Nakuru
Bishop Cora you talk about mint mission
window go to Virata so Mustafa kukuku
topic we become showmen gotaga m osika
hello youtube unit Oh Bonnie one as we
go talkin akuto cocky javi
who talked abou Ambu who talked about in
go to talk to e go to agra tala quango
to toggle the red to talkin hi Ravi
kutaro well done my coffee
well anyway - ma cherie
- Tucker Wanda Burundi Pangolin Ian I
see your Excellencies in my panda
milanesa go Wanda Burundi so their
leaders are here the machining Gumo very
good America talk abou rune Dima coffee
I see Rudy at 12:08 Waldo to talk abou
Ronde first thing GU talker Wanda amen
well done now my family two men and a
mom who you 43 years ago so - well she
sued Salewa our professors knotek Terry
our Molly muah more University that
Terry Aldo retroviral who you know when
a guy who unit miss Dana way to fate
Holly a
olavo when a Pendergast you have a new
soul let me show me on a PhD I owe you a
night were captain Andrew annihilation
day who you who you are now equal
engineer David and a you are computer
messages a an arrestable wanna a severe
that's my family thank you very much
[Applause]
original mutata yaki
okay I will begin my shirt speech and
then I call the bishop to say a short
speech and then assistant and the rest
we will finish by 12:40 we are done
12:40 I want us to finish your
excellency president way to not w to
work on today is a very special day for
me to hand over leadership in peaceful
manner
Thank You members of Barossa GU for
supporting me for 18 years during my 18
years in leadership I have seen a IC
crow from 3,800 churches to 8400 judges
[Applause]
AIC is spread from Ayala tool a doctor
from lunga lunga to malaga from latvia
to loiter from guarantee achieve from
vocal to McWeeny
and all the cities of kenya from the VAM
lon we tangled discharge is well spread
as a committed team in my office we have
we were able to achieve the following we
expanded our hospital ministry across
the nation and is providing good
services to the citizens of this country
furthermore it is creating jobs for
Kenyans
we have acquired property and develop
others today AIC properties especially
in Adobe where I was stationed is what
six million six billion shillings and in
Sepang to pay salaries for the workers
our schools
professor maja splay spread all over the
country you know it
we are big steigleder all the
specialists take old us in this country
we have 2800 primary schools we have
1070 schools and indeed we thank God for
opening this opportunity for us our
women fraternity have embarked on a
conference your excellency which you
know you came and helped them the
conference center is 40 percent complete
and we hope it will be completed we were
able to start people EOS m of which you
excellency I know you are a van
sigmoidal Anita buta qua Simone it is an
independent radio and I sang Matangi is
the one who gave me some licenses when
he was there thank you so much today
people Yahoo same acabas the whole
country and we have a TV station
operated in red we have we were able to
impress devolve type of leadership and
we created twenty eight areas led by
bishops and it has he is the Lord in my
office
we also empowered women who are left
behind for a long time now our ladies
are will pastas like the rest of the
menfolk
we have also built over the years a
strong human force of pastas 7,200
pastas from 3,000 when I came in this
men and women are planting churches all
over the country with not only plant
churches in Kenya alone during my
leadership we planted also in Rwanda
Burundi DR Congo and other places our
Bible training colleges have expanded
and our strongest emphasis is to Train
men and women missions is our core value
our national machinery folk tours from
my office and those from other areas are
200 families serving in enriched areas
of this country our University Scott as
Kron when I came we had only 50 students
right now we have 3000 and over with the
God as I have said your excellency we
tried our level best to be tax compliant
and we are up to date with Tang God we
had our share of problems as you know I
remember I was told a story of your
father and muru at it they were each met
so when they take all the jab and move
at a trauma Miyagi not a chomo mando
Auriga Hogan I hope even a son become a
pillow on assume wha me me Abba Ambu Ala
Moana and yo yo yo ksama a bee Waja to
le soleil Mutoh a to Auriga achoo
so Ava's a manga mundo Auriga Oh comon
goony wanna handle a pyjama
mugambi Ivana shi'ite Angela to go go
Quino
so have a human Armani
so I actually I had share of problems I
want to tell you that I don't want to
say a SV has been a bed of roses
I had shell problems had God cases I had
what of you but only know the grace of
God was efficient our spiritual matters
we can say is maturing enough you can
see this fair and many others we
are doing a lot of emphasis in teaching
to charge discipleship departments
Sunday school and always see a more
common saying Sunday school that is our
core value we love Sunday school so the
church is growing today as I leave this
responsibility
I have built carefully on the strong
foundation laid by our forefathers any
achievement caused to my master Jesus
Christ whom I pledged to serve and I
quote the words of a woman who came in
the year to 1903 she said the only thing
worth living on or dying for is winning
souls or winning this world back to God
again if there were no one else to do it
I will do it I have done that in my life
I want to thank God that he has seen me
through I want to thank my master who
who tells me after these great
achievements you have achieved in I see
there is a cotton looked 1710 so say
when you have done this say I've done
everything I was told to do I am and
what a seven I have only discharged my
duty so I don't pride in anything as I
live I see I want to say i discharged my
duty and I thank God
as I conclude my speech I want to thank
the government of Kenya all governments
so Magan Adam president my press Thank
You Becky
Preston guru why am I saying this you
know people don't know I love history
president Kenyatta Toma open the way for
the gospel of Jesus Christ to reach
transia was in issue and other places by
helping farmers to acquire the former
white islands otherwise in healing a gun
handy in kagamiku you Inga comma Holly
Hagen yatta a newbie rubaba miss Lu
Bolivia okay a defender Garcia key today
when you go to US English you 600 judges
Catala 400 judges happy we had no child
before guru in those places but when you
say open up to say Africans were in the
salsa do churches become a together the
under wah is a good example we want to
thank Maui who stood by the church
throughout his lifetime whenever I go in
this town people want a free criminal
ship wah Mui when only some insane I
mean I got a minimum be a misery because
they know because they know we stayed
with him he serve discharge with
dedication
what about Kibaki Kibaki helped us I
remember there is a building here and
missed his Excellency Alonzo knows there
was a problem but give ugly one day
where
communion torn Molly away knew what
channel are you
I wonder tango a president who you are
sitting in a house you go in tribute it
immensely we remember when you came here
it was just a shell
I remember you walking with me there and
you say this is massive because giving
us a yo-yo cabeza la nuit today it is
just a beautiful building thank you your
excellency you upon we have come to the
tally you have helped us a lot
the women folk are so grateful the same
maturity Beauty he has been a great help
to us great help to us
I cannot mention you know you at a
beauty and me are very close I married
this too so when I see them sitting like
this
I'm so proud one thing I have not
received your excellency and I don't
want to receive instead of state
commendation
Preston mo never gave me and he was my
friend
Preston g-body never gave me and now I
am living do you know I don't want it
I'm saying
these people saw me as a pasta and I
want to be seen like that same mood to
am by an otaku find this way give me to
open this one up on a semi head of state
commendation what I used to have a
garage a yo I thank that I want to thank
God my sustainer my father I thank you
God thank you so much I didn't know I
was one day I will stand here thank you
for understanding members of our isaku I
want to thank Milla man in my church I
want to thank my great family this great
family loved me so much and they have
given me support I needed I want to
thank prayer partners prayer partners in
Kenya people who loved me so much
I want to thank international supporters
have seen the CUDA here and many others
I want to thank local supporters when I
was doing work in Rwanda most of you
here contributed I know I don't want to
mention names but you helped me I want
to thank you so much for trusting me a
man from Rwanda knows you gave me seven
million shillings
we bought land so I never used it so it
is great I want to thank my driver for
23 years I had only one driver
[Applause]
if makutano is here you understand for
people to see you that is my driver for
23 years that man I had a ha house help
call Sammy a true Khanna for 23 years
also I want to thank them under thank my
colleagues who worked with me in the
office deputy presiding bishop rev range
of repertory can you stand brother we
clap for you where are you thank you so
much
the lead abraham moonwalk wrote down the
angle rotation wrote assad 5 3 4 p shops
mystic allah who has been reading daniel
Matua format raja some way notice since
I'm on Odeon de ceremonia my present
secretary and all that the bat mental
heads
I want to thank you so much so much so
much under thank even the cleaners who
are helping me all these men and women
shaft with dedication and worked with me
in total loyalty coated with Brotherhood
as I conclude I want to thank my great
charge I see this great judge I see I
love you I see thank you so much members
of AIC I say a big thank you to you
supporting me loving me some bringing me
samake some bringing me Kuroshio so I'm
bringing me my MA
some bringing me which Kikuyu some
bringing me any your Excellencies one
day through Canali changing a legion
jogando now where and again so aleppo
quand la la Vega Vito and a security
officer my enemy nagamma Mian in Yama
what about that isn't that something I
wonder thank God for her
Kirito for bringing me chai and Nandi
and meat from acai and even Marsabit
windy great mango and so forth you see
they have a very good mix flour and so
forth aha what can I say yeah I see
thank you rather than wasting time I'm
telling you all this
may I say thank you to all of you and
thank you for coming today thank you all
for supporting me I love you too
I'll be continuing to work I'll tell my
friend rule that I'm not looking for a
job I'm done I am a missionary so a
missionary will not look for jobs so if
you give me one I'll turn down I will
not be a German of anything I want to
continue doing the missionary work in
Rwanda Burundi Central Africa Republic
and in other places if you people want
to support me send some money Togo me me
I will appreciate loggin engine ammonia
wanna Alberici now the presiding bishop
come and say your brief remarks can we
appreciate to our presided bishop thank
you
to our chief guest his Excellency the
President of the Republic of Kenya the
commander in chief the son of the first
president of the Republic of Kenya the
Jomo Kenyatta
we want to say thank you for finding
time at a time like this
when we are so busy to come and be with
us to our deputy president dr. William
Ruto members of Senate who are here
members of parliament cabinet
secretaries and all protocols observed
we are grateful for being with us and
above our achieve guest speaker at
Bishop Moussa
thank you retired at Bishop Daniel thank
you to ahora comrades have a katana
despite that your mom Dave your mom
today's are going to be with a lot you
are still with us yeah we will
appreciate
prayers are with you and we control with
you to all other clergy members from
Rhonda Burundi Bishop Doctore Lunati of
gospel church representative of
salvation hammy with us yeah we will say
thank you for coming and now draw
presiding bishop our good friend dr.
Cyrus Diego members of Bourassa pou
bishops the pastas the clergy the
congregation gathered here today
good afternoon I will be very brief
there was a former Tanzanian president
who came to Kenya one day and he had
just been installed as the president of
Tanzania his Excellency Kaaba
and they want to quote his words he said
women wanna Molly a mile away Jana now
Queen a click a kill Emily me so I won't
have much to say please allow me to be
very brief and I hope you all understand
I want to take this opportunity to thank
God for the grace and the mercy he has
extended to every one of us gathered
here in this sanctuary today this is
indeed a great moment in the history of
our church in Kenya allow me to say
something about the great Shama
because that is the only word I will
mention this afternoon great Shama or
great earring comes from Deuteronomy 6:4
as four and five this is the time the
law was repeated to the nation of Israel
and they were about to go to the land of
Canaan as God promised and this is what
the scripture says here how Israel the
Lord our God the Lord is one you shall
love the Lord your God with all your
heart and with oh you are saw and with
all your strength in this text the Lord
God summarizes the heart of religion to
every nation because the fear of the
Lord in the heart of men is and will be
the most powerful principle of obedience
if we fear God irrespective of our
religion then that is the greatest
principle that a nation can feel
accommodated and the reason I say this
here is the necessity they entail or the
demand of any religion in any kind
in any family is the best demand or
entail and therefore I urge each and
every one of us because in Christianity
and righteousness we advance and it
secures the prosperity of any people in
any country if we advance to here and
allow the Lord we will not need the
Inspector General of Police and
therefore I kindly request each and
every one of us that we love the Lord
with all our heart and with all our soul
and with all our strength and the rest
will be done because this is the
principle of faith the God we serve is a
God who is Jehovah Jehovah who is
infinite a Jehovah who is eternally
perfect Jehovah who is self-existent at
the overall is self-sufficient this is
the message there ho we must hear it
requires us to love God with our heart
with our soul and with our strength and
this is the trick atomic of a man
expressed in the love of God because
love is the demonstration of God's
character by which he falender will
commits himself and gives himself always
to seek the good for the highest order
of his people and therefore God's love
is always unfailing is always a deserved
is always an ending did we do this then
this church
and this country will continue to higher
level let's be remind that I'll make a
short one minute appeal of to appeal
number one the words of Jesus Christ in
Matthew 28:18 2:20 we are commanded
about the Great Commission all of us
must obey this great command if we love
him as a Church of Jesus Christ we are
called to proclaim the gospel of Jesus
Christ in all the earth and this is our
primary duty all of us
I urge all of us to move above and
beyond our comfort zone and a preach
Christ to all men as appeal number one
appeal number two is also equally as
born this scripture in Matthew 13 first
one to 17 we must offer prayers to our
leaders in our country for it is
commanded and must be done in love we
must pray for this country we must pray
for the president we must pray for his
government we must pray for the three
arms of the government and we must pray
for the neighbor love your neighbor as
yourself we must pray them for our
economy and our social order across the
country and our political stability our
health our peace our security and the
prosperity of the nation cleaner at that
moment I'm reminded I once what and a
famous relative of his Excellency the
president as is
young man in those days 74 up to 78 dr.
Muraki shahe I worked with him for four
years there are days we would go in
those holidays to her back either on
20th first day of May or first day of
June or trellis and there is something
that all of us we must do the first
president would speak and address the
nation and at the hand at the end
something peculiar with the him he would
say say one ing what Rock evoke mingle
append that ope
a ram be turtle Sandoval Anora Hanukkah
Carrara knock or array and then he would
say and then you this is my point
get it were right and I wanted to send
that appeal to canons I would say
whatever was the subject of the day
whether it is angle cultural show
whether it is a school after making the
three armies he would mentioned the
appear I am appealing to the cannons we
must pray for the stability of our
economy if it were those days by then I
was not a pasta if it were those days
then I would have today say it but
Cinetopia around a tattoo Sam Guevara
and then at last I would say now
security now he told me what he'll wear
to ära and then we would say and you
know from that repetitive practice our
country grew to a point that it was the
hike on of the nations in Africa I'm
appealing to you now as a clergy we must
offer our prayers
to the government we must offer our
prayers to the institutions of this
country because the moment we stand in
the dark the nation of the Republic of
Kenya will grow economically socially
politically to higher Heights that we
will be adamant by the other nations
that is my appeal number two then as I
close today is a great day and I want to
convey my gratitude to the Barossa coup
of Africa inland charge Kenya for the
support faith and hope that you have
accorded me I'm just a mere man a fee
night one in every way and today I
beseech you to help hold me in prayer
and the support as we work together
secondly I want today also to say to my
family they have supported me for a very
long time my wife my children want to
thank them for their support and love in
this ministry and I keep on asking them
to continue accommodated me and the
particularly when I find myself at home
at 11 p.m. those of us who don't know I
serve a kijiji slum Church in pipeline
one of the greatest se congregations in
eastern central Africa and the only
people the only people you can find them
past 8:00 p.m. wanting to see their
pasta please come regi pipeline you find
them there during the day you never find
them they are hard-working
but in the evening that is the time they
needed a pasta
and therefore my family has put up with
me at such a moment and I want to thank
them I also want to thank that Church AC
pipeline family for the support and we
say thank you thank you
a I see Mel Imani for hosting us today I
know you have done a lot of work may God
bless you oh my god Shane his face to
you and it was as he can I am aware of
the expectations in this position I
implore you
o that we were the full armor of Christ
praying for each other supporting each
other in this journey of faith I will
need your Morrow and the spiritual
support to lead our church to the next
level to our government your excellency
sir you have heard that just last week
you are registered that's how quick it
is in the Attorney General and we want
to thank your government for supporting
the church we are grateful we have never
been frustrated by the institutions of
the government of the Republic of Kenya
thank you government of the Republic of
kena
through the leadership of his Excellency
the president for Canada for supporting
this great congregation lasts lastly but
by no means not the least to our
outgoing presiding bishop until yes is
not a small thing that's quite something
and your family we want to thank you for
your guidance for your mentorship
may the Lord God fella and I bless you
and increase you if at all you say you
don't want to be appointed as chairman
you have made it very clear and nobody
ever speaks of himself now
speaking on your behalf to the president
your excellency Sir William say a pair
MBs not a booty work you two pegasi I'm
a funny matter type ellika attract a
guitar to the Bieber to malaga guitar
legwork Avenue in here so we kindly
request you to leave your door open for
more consultation we'll be popping him
and now may the Lord God of peace who
brought up our Lord Jesus Christ from
the dead the great Shepherd of the sheep
through the blood of everlasting
covenant make you complete in every good
work to do his will working in you what
is well pleasing in his sight through
Jesus to whom be glory for ever and ever
amen may God bless you I now call deputy
presiding bishop all crew to make his
opening speech
Carlos Ana's Cove
my um - I'm Connor I got new guinea
I'm Mikasa Cooper's Anna like in a nacho
coup you Excellency the President of the
Republic of Kenya you excellency the
deputy president your excellency my
friend
come on some Chaka our breeze her dad
presiding bishop Daktari yeah whoa the
deciding bishops who are here our guest
speaker distinguished guests the entire
congregation I want to keep greet you in
the name of our Lord and Savior Jesus
Christ
good afternoon today is a very special
day for me and my family and I want to
see her here please come please come
please come
we are young as I am but she she I don't
know whether my first phone thought I
see this is in 30 I know in university
Natron go I don't know why she's around
come Anu please come our gimmick okay
should knock off on for from three and
from one but my phone got chopped up
there is mercy can you please come
I'm young as cheese so she's now turning
20 22 years 21 and so and we are married
now 20 22 years ago I want to thank my
family I know the extended family are
here I want to appreciate you for
keeping me strong standing with me and I
want to say thank you very much
I want to thank Almighty God for calling
me
you can now sit for calling me to the
ministry and giving me the opportunity
to serve this great child call Africa
inland charge Kenya I'm glad to have
been given honor by God and the central
check-ins Council to serve as the deputy
presiding bishop my role is to assist
the presiding bishop so that the mission
of Africa England judge is achieved here
on occasion wonka know we are very
thankful for the founders of our charge
for giving us a great mission from
Matthew 28 verse 19 through 20 which
focuses us to preach the good news of
our Lord Jesus Christ to all the world
or all the nation this is my passion
with the able with the help from God we
will endeavor to reach out with the good
news of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ
mission is a mandate from God and I want
to ask all the members of African
language to support us in this endeavor
I want to thank the retired presiding
bishop dr. reyga he has been a great
blessing to our church he has also been
a great
model to me yes I've discharged with the
dedication may Almighty God bless you as
you transition in serving God in serving
him in a different capacity as my
brother presiding bishop had said in God
walk there is not a man we serve him
until he comes to take us home or we
meet in the air I want to congratulate
and thank our presiding bishop Reverend
abramova for taking up the mantle of
leading the Africa on Chaya Kenya I
promise you my brother that you have my
prayers and support
I also want to thank Bourassa ku and the
entire charge of trusting me with this
great responsibility to my area jake
onson the my RCC and home local church
and my district are canceled I thank you
for supporting me in ministry for the
many years I have served God god bless
you god bless Kenyon
I of a special tongue to offer special
thanks and my gratitude to my wife and
my children who have been strong pillars
and source of inspiration to me to all
my relatives and close friends
thank you all may God bless you to the
members of African land charge thank you
for your prayers and support I and my
brother well why we request that you
continue praying for us let's unite
together love one another and put our
energy in serving our recent Lord Jesus
Christ
Wharton martyr Martin Luther King jr.
once he says that darkness cannot drive
out darkness only light can do that
let's pray the cosmos and the word of
God will deliver this nation the Word of
God will deliver our families the Word
of God will deliver everyone and we will
see success you continue to say head
cannot drive out hate only love can do
that let's love one another
that's unite for the betterment of our
church let's unite for the betterment of
our country because laugh can bring
success and good for the nation
god bless you thank you I thought that
we will call our families together now
you have done let me call my so may I
have this privilege to call my wife and
my children
please come all of you for the like
thank you your excellency at Rockaway
Hashanah those who would like to give me
three goats they are two remaining you
can still see me after the service this
is my wife rosemary 0 first Bond Paul is
my son-in-law and everything Gina the
wife Esther who came a day she she's
cooling in the UK a ph.d program and a
massive that's so big the families in
actual fact when up when - Earl a number
in a buggy who could see key a key to an
appeal Calello and rival Kim BIA
otherwise we want to thank them for
supporting us may God bless you
[Music]
Pattin aphasia whom chose among guna
Wamba
- oh me Asante a - to knock opened
asana casaba Bowie tupa SEC Kwanzaa me
to Baraka sonikku za o yama niyama so
January Sheeran is rainy not no Sakura
wanna kuta Nam Sri nominee he purchases
Oh Toto Akko katika Safari Zozo t na
Hitachi Kula namazi - Takashi Ricky
ahmadiya Mungo am been gonna knock you
see here combi routine Delia go to cydia
san cartega tunisia Nakata can Chia
Kenya - Sadie's Asahara to Nepal and
Elena Mambo main Guinea or teh maracas
ACOs cabeza quad Juliet ro assassin in
Oaxaca cata Kimiko no among go anyways
Akua Linda Nene no TMZ aqua aqua
smashing belly otro fois que Bella mama
cat kafra KU pikir ke moko Saavedra
iesous christos Vanuatu otaku Funari
tango Mele
NASA na hitomi Larry animal La Mina
waters a satirical name name yahwah no
Atreus Christo nama Penzias moon no
shirokova room talkative oh ok nasty
salty SAS
nina budd equating the born
[Music]